verilymag.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Verily

Altstream Media LLC (“Altstream”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive via our Service (as defined in the Terms of Service Agreement available at http://www.verilymag.com/terms-of-service from users of our Service. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Service. Your use of the Service following any such notice will signify and constitute your assent to and acceptance of such revised Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, capitalized terms used herein have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the products or services of our business partners or to any other third parties, even if their products or services are linked to, or embedded within, our Service. For example, we may provide social media features as part of our Service that enables you to share information with your connections on third party social networking platforms. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We recommend that you review the privacy statements of the other parties with whom you interact before submitting your information.

1\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE  
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means information that can be used to uniquely identify you, such as your name, address and e-mail address.

 _Personal Information We Collect_  
When you interact with us, we may ask you to supply us with Personal Information. For example, when you place an order, subscribe to newsletters or promotional materials, or otherwise use our Service, we may ask you to provide information such as your name, address, and/or e-mail address.

 _Our Use of Your Personal Information_  
We mainly use your Personal Information, either alone or in combination with other information, so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our Service and related content, products, and marketing efforts.  
The following are examples of a variety of ways that we may use your Personal Information. We may use your Personal Information:

* to provide you with the best user experience possible;  
* to provide the products and services you purchase, respond to your questions, and carry out the transactions you have requested;  
* to communicate with you regarding Service updates, offers, orders, alerts, promotions, and events;  
* to help us develop, customize, deliver, support and improve our Service, products, content, and advertising;  
* to administer promotions and contests;  
* to protect the rights or property of Altstream or our users, and prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities;  
* to protect the security of our products, services, and business;  
* for our internal purposes (such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and communications); and  
* otherwise, as disclosed to you at the point of collection.  
If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow any unsubscribe instructions that may be provided in our communications to you. Please note that we may use your Personal Information to contact you with important notifications, such as notices with respect to purchases, safety, or changes to our terms, conditions, and policies; you may not opt out of these notifications. If you have any questions or would like to remove your Personal Information from our databases, please let us know by contacting us at ohhello@verilymag.com and we will assist you with the process.

 _Public Forums_  
We may offer blog features, or similar public forums where you and other users of our Service can post content or otherwise communicate. The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information (including personally identifiable information about any person) in connection with your use of public forums. We may use Personal Information and other information about you to identify you with a posting in a public forum. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by other persons, including third parties that do not adhere to the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Service.

 _Collection and Use of Non-Identifying Information_  
We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose information in a form that does not personally identify you (“Non-Identifying Information”) for any purpose. Non-Identifying Information can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. We and/or our third party service providers obtain Non-Identifying Information about you from information that you provide us, either separately or together with your Personal Information. We and/or our third party service providers also automatically collect certain Non-Identifying Information from you when you access our Service.

Certain Non-Identifying Information about you would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers in a way that enables you to be identified. However, the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other Non-Identifying information. We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other users or sources to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of our products and services, and to analyze and understand how our products and services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically.

 _Non-Identifying Information We Automatically Collect_  
When you access our Service, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies, now and hereafter devised, that automatically record certain usage information. This information may include your Internet Protocol address (and other unique identifiers for the particular device you use to access the Internet), browser type, your web or application request, your interaction with our Service, the webpage or other feature you were using before you came to our Service, pages of our Website that you visit, information you search for via our Service, access times and dates, and other similar information. We may use this information for a variety of purposes, including analyzing and enhancing our products and services, and to help personalize our Service for you. We do not treat this information as Personal Information (except to the extent required by local law), although if we combine it with the Personal Information you provide, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information. We and our third-party service providers may automatically collect Non-Identifying Information using various methods, including, without limitation, cookies.

A cookie is a small data file transferred to your computer (or other device) when it is used to access our Service. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including to enable certain features of our Service, to better understand how you interact with our Service and to monitor aggregate usage by visitors and online traffic routing. You may be able to instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the online services you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of our online services or all functionality of our online services.

2\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE  
Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of Altstream unless we have received your consent. Non-Identifying Information may be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 _Our Service Providers and Other Third Parties_  
We may engage third party companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf (e.g., without limitation, payment processing, software maintenance services, e-mail notifications, product delivery services, database management, web analytics and other services). These third parties may have access to your Personal Information. If they do, this access is provided so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are not authorized by us to otherwise use or disclose your Personal Information, except to the extent required by law.

 _Compliance with Laws, Legal Process and Authorities_  
We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of us or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable.

 _Data Transfer_  
Altstream processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. Your Personal Information may be transferred to, and used by, entities located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Such export is a requirement of providing your information to Altstream, and you hereby consent to such export.

 _Business Transfers_  
Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, we may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose some or all of our assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. It’s Altstream’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

3\. GENERAL.  
 _Changing or Deleting Your Information_  
Alstream makes good faith efforts to provide individuals with reasonable access to Personal Information that they have provided to Altstream and the reasonable ability to review and correct it or ask for deletion, as applicable, if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. Access requests may be sent via e-mail to ohhello@verilymag.com. Please note we may retain server/backup copies of all such data, and that we may decline to process change or deletion requests that we deem to be unreasonable, or require disproportionate technical effort, or jeopardize the privacy of others.

 _Security_  
We employ appropriate security measures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction. These security measures include administrative, technical, and physical precautions to safeguard your Personal Information against loss, theft, and misuse. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your Personal Information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information.

 _Third Party Products and Services_  
Our products and services may contain links to, or content from, third party websites and other products and services. The fact that we link to a website or display an advertisement or other third party content is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with any of those third parties, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices.

We do not exercise control over third party websites, products or services including, without limitation, third party payment service providers. These other products and services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer or other device, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other persons and entities, including, without limitation, third party payment processors, follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the information you submit to them or they collect from you. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

 _Our Policy Toward Children_  
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 via our services, and do not target our online services to children under 13. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.

 _Changes to this Privacy Policy_  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect such changes and revise the effective date included at the end of this policy.

 _Contacting Us_  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us via e-mail to ohhello@verilymag.com.

 _Privacy Policy Effective Date: July 9, 2012_
